Gu Group is stalling
They haven't covered the real cash flow
They are using new collaborations
to cover old deficits
Just like before
On the surface it's an explanation
but they're actually just shifting the risks
Lu Group and the bank share this view
So Gu Group
sent another visit request this morning
It's Gu Chengze again
It's not a business visit this time
It's a private invitation for Mrs Fu
Want to see him
I'll see him
Mrs Fu, Gu Chengze is desperate right now
He might not just want to talk about the past
I know
That's exactly why I need to see him
He wants to disguise his regret as true love
I don't want to give him space to keep
deluding himself
Mr Fu, are you being protective of your wife